[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
'Life as a Major' theme song]
(Lee Young) Come to your senses, mother.
[nervous music]
(Eunju) Teacher...
I'm sleepy
No, you can't sleep.
[Eunju’s labored breathing]
Open your eyes, okay?
It's so cold
(Lee Young) Just be patient.
Mother, what is your name? What is your name?
Seo... Eunju
Where are we?
(Lee Young) Mother!
Mother, what day is it today?
What day is it today?
Your second child was born today.
second birthday
October...
16th...
That's right, just be patient.
[Urgent music]
(Eunwon) Please give me more blood
Please also administer FFP.
[Beep sound]
(Sanghyun) It’s CPR!
Please do compression
(Eunwon) You guys pack, cover the boat.
[Beeping sound]
(Sanghyun) Please bring me an emergency cart.
- (Yunjeong) Yes!
- (Lee Young) Roll gauze.
Firefighting
I'll change hands
[ECG alarm sound]
[Eunwon’s heavy breathing]
(Sanghyeon) Please give me epinephrine
[ECG stop sound]
[Eunju’s husband cries]
(Eunju’s mother) Your bastards...
[sad music]
I have to feed them and give them hugs.
[Eunju’s husband cries]
I wanted to see you so much...
[Eun-ju’s husband and Eun-ju’s mother cry]
(Eunju’s mother) [Sobbing] Eunju!
(Eunju’s husband) [Sobbing] Honey!
[Sound of water drops]
(Eunju’s name) Eunju!
[Sound of blood pouring]
[nervous music]
[Lee Young’s surprised gasp]
[Lee Young’s embarrassed exclamation]
[Lee Young’s heavy breathing]
[Eun-joo mocks crying]
[Sound of water drops]
[Sound effect of being sucked in]
[Lee Young’s surprised moan]
[Rough breathing]
[sigh]
[light sigh]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
'Life as a Major' theme song]
[siren sound]
[Calm music]
Oh, Teacher Dahye went on vacation.
Uh, because of the death of the entire mother.
You were so shocked.
[Sound of pencil case zipper closing]
He just cried for days and days.
It's worth it
That day, he and I
Did you see Bed passing by?
Even though I saw that for a moment, I still have nightmares.
(Sabi) The mother lost a lot of blood.
They said they removed the uterus and gave nearly 30 pieces of blood.
Because DIC finally came
There was no way to do anything about it, right?
Ugh
(Jae-il) I am in the world
I hate postpartum hemorrhage the most.
Why is something like that happening?
(Jeongmin) So why does that happen?
(together) Hello?
(Jeongmin) You don’t know, right?
Moreover, whether the mother will develop PPH or not.
We can't predict in advance, right?
'Cause we can't make it bleed
If you bleed, you have to react well.
To do that, you have to study a lot.
So for the next month
I'm going to study two days a week.
(together) Ah, professor
(Jeongmin) The response is better than expected?
So shall we do it three times?
This week, when PPH occurs
about what we can do
I'm going to study
What is this?
(Sabi) Ah, the other day, Professor Gong Gong-seon
This is the material you taught in PPH class.
[Sound of paper turning]
(Jeongmin) Um...
Not this
- Look at this.
- (Residing in Japan) Yes
(Jeongmin) Now, from today
I'm going to do something very important
Practical to learn with your body, not your head
So, starting today, either doze off or sleep.
[Growling sound effect]
[Squeaking sound]
If you do something else, they won’t leave you alone?
(Lee Young) Yes
[Lee Young clears his throat]
firstly
(Jeongmin) The most important thing in PPH is
Recognize bleeding quickly
It's moving fast.
(Steamboat) PPH?
- I already lectured you on that, right?
- (Nanjing) Yes
(Kiseon) I did it, but why only the lyrics...
No, is Professor Seo Jeong-min doing it again?
(Namkyung) Oh, something happened last time too.
This time, focusing on actual practice.
Easier to understand...
(Kiseon) Easy?
So was what I taught you before difficult?
no
[Kiseon snorts]
No, what difference does it make if you teach your own class?
Showing off in many ways
Oh my, you're so good, really
Our surgery is at 3 o'clock later?
(Namkyung) Oh, that’s it
Today, Professor Seo Jeong-min has 6 surgeries.
I did it because there was an emergency section in the middle.
Uh, that other surgery.
Spinal fail
There was a delay in switching to General.
So?
When do I do it?
Around 5 o'clock
I gave it to the mother.
What?
Hey, I have surgery today.
Wait until 5 o'clock to do this?
(Namkyung) Ah...
Uh, the operating room priority is today.
This is Professor Seo Jeong-min.
[Awesome exclamation]
You are the leader today, right?
Are you going to do whatever you want?
Oh, I hate it!
Ask the anesthesiologist to open another room.
Uh, after that GS surgery.
(Nanjing) Around 3 o’clock, both ways
They say it seems possible.
That too
It is said that Professor Seo Jeong-min writes it.
(Kiseon) No, I gave them both ways.
Of course I should write it
Why do you use it all yourself, why?
[light music]
No way
Are you having a fight with me now?
no
There was so much surgery today.
It seems like you're out of your mind...
Lee Young says
At 6:30 in the evening with the hospital director
Because you have a meeting
Until then, you must be out.
Please understand
Why is he meeting the hospital director?
I don't know much about that either.
(Kiseon) Mr...
Seo Jeong-min, I have surgery at 3 o'clock
Tell them you have to do it
No way at 5 o'clock
And you must get to the operating room.
Okay?
Ah...
[sigh]
What should you do with me?
(Jeongmin) To Professor Gong Gong-seon
Did I tell you that the surgery was delayed?
(Lee Young) Yes, I did it.
At the last time as scheduled
I was told to have surgery.
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Jeongmin) He did that?
Why don't you say something?
(Lee Young) I don’t know
First of all, I have to live and see.
So the professor
Let's go out at 6 o'clock
You told me to make it
If I don't do that, I'll get scolded...
(Jeongmin) Did you do well?
What's going on?
[Interesting music]
(Nanjing) Hey, next Tuesday
Professor Gong Gong-seon adds an induction.
(Lee Young) No
That day, Professor Seo Jeong-min also told me to do induction.
(Nanjing) No
Professor Seo Jeong-min on Monday
There are 3 induction stations.
We have to do two on tuesday
You don't have many mothers.
I can do it on Thursday.
Um, I have a conference next Thursday.
you do it on thursday
Hey, Seo Jeong-min...
(Lee Young) Isn’t Cheem going to the conference?
- If you don't catch it on Tuesday, there'll be a fuss.
- Then what about Kong?
Doesn’t Kong’s personality make you crazy?
Icy, annoying, tsk.
Oh, they can just say it.
Are you going to make fun of us?
(Nanjing) So
Hey
But aren’t professors a bit strange these days?
It was strange to begin with, and it remains strange as ever.
Oh, by the way
Wow, I think I've been doing it more lately.
What?
A bloody rivalry
childishly
(Nanjing) No
One person gets upset even if Seo Jeong-min’s name is mentioned.
If the other one is an airship,
I definitely said no, huh?
Yeah, for no reason we end up dying in the middle.
What is this, really?
hello, hello
(Nanjing) What is it?
[Sound of cabinet opening]
What, why did you come back?
Professor Lim Dong-ju’s emergency sex session
It's your turn with your wife.
(Sabi) Uh, I finished my work with my wife.
When I'm done, I have to leave work.
Oh, why are you looking at obstetric surgery?
(Sabi) It’s an incarnation case.
How do I get home?
How do I get home, I need to get home quickly
(Sabi) That’s a really rare case.
If it's not now, I might never see it again
[Lee Young sighs]
Are you guys really not going?
(Lee Young) I have to go
(Nanjing) Home
Okay, goodbye.
(Sabi) Hello?
(Junmo) Yes
The ward work is finished.
Why don't you get off work?
(Sabi) I have a surgery I want to see.
(Junmo) Even when I don’t come home from work
Is this a surgery you really want to see?
(Sabi) Yes
(Junmo) Yes, this is not an easy surgery.
Uh, the approach is also unique.
In the eyes of medical residents
These hand movements are also very amazing, uh
(Sabi) I think you’re really amazing.
[Junmo’s light smile]
- (Junmo) What?
- (Sabi) Then!
[Program operation sound effect]
(Junmo) Where are you going?
The operating room has changed, it's here
(Sabi) Isn’t it?
This is Professor Lim Dong-ju’s section number 6.
[light music]
[Junmo’s laughter]
(Junmo) Hey
You, it's your turn with your wife now.
(Sabi) Yes, but incarnation
Because it was special from the beginning
I really want to see you
See you tomorrow
[Button operation sound]
[Sound of door opening]
[Junmo’s laughter]
(Junmo) Well...
Oh, he really can't do it.
[rattling sound]
Hey!
It hasn't even been set up yet
Why are you telling me to come down!
(Residence in Japan) Ah
Should I have gone to see the surgery too?
(Lee Young) You said you had a promise?
(Jae-il) Are promises important now?
It's a very rare case?
Incarcer... round?
(Lee Young) Surrction
(Jaeil) Uh, yeah, that
(Lee Young) Is it true that you want to see the surgery?
(Nanjing) Write, that is.
You're not having surgery.
Don’t you want to see that hello girl?
(Jaeil) What, why do I miss her?
(Namkyung) No, these days you
He's always chasing after Sabi.
Just in case
(Japan) When should I?
(Lee Young) Ever since the day after I went to the karaoke bar
(Namkyung) Yes
(Japan) No
October is now over and it will soon be two years.
If you're next to Sabi
Are you going to study a bit?
And he's good at explaining things.
So that it fits your ears, yeah
(Nankyung) I understand
If you two are going to date
be the first to tell us
But we still see each other 16 hours a day, huh?
[cell phone ringing sound]
You'll be sad if other people hear about it.
(Japan) Are you writing a drama?
You're talking nonsense.
yes
Former hospital...
Oh! Yes, it's me...
(Lee Young) It’s good
yes
(Namkyung) Huh?
[Call end sound]
Who?
Are you by any chance?
Brother-in-law
[cute music]
brother-in-law
(Lee Young) My brother-in-law stopped by on the way.
To take you there
(Residence in Japan) Huh? Then let's go
Can't you just drop me off at the bus stop?
Ah, it's the way to go anyway.
Hey, me too, me too
Uh, right now
I would like to say hello to your brother-in-law.
- No!
- (Japan) Hey
(Nanjing) Why?
No way
I have something to talk about with my brother-in-law.
It's a family story
Uh, then I'll cover my ears and go.
- (Residing in Japan)
- Yeah, me too.
No way
Hey, I really
I don't even have the strength to walk, huh?
- (Lee Young) No, no.
- Oh, what's wrong?
My brother-in-law...
I'm shy
(Lee Young) With someone I don’t know
I really hate riding in a car together.
Next time, next time, I'll give you a ride
go
[Nankyung’s puzzled breathing]
Oh Iyoung, you
It's disgusting
(Nanjing) Let’s go!
(Residence in Japan) See you tomorrow
It's disgusting
[sigh]
[lively music]
Well...
Come?
(Dowon) What, what?
rice?
go?
I missed you too!
Stay in the car?
Aren't we riding together?
Well, what don’t you do?
So you're saying stay in the car?
Come quickly!
What are you going to do if someone sees it?
[bright music]
(Dowon) What do you see?
Are you saying the houses are facing the same direction?
(Lee Young) At the time, it was okay because it was real.
That's because it's not right now.
[Dowon’s laughter]
(Dowon) What does that mean?
Even then and now, the house is in the same direction.
no
I'm afraid there will be rumors that we are dating.
(Lee Young) It’s not done yet.
(Dowon) Why?
There was a rumor that they were dating
Are you worried about what will happen if we break up soon?
Oh, isn't it?
Oh, you're not going to break up?
[Dowon’s laughter]
no
First-year kids don’t know anything.
Still, I wonder if I should tell you first.
(Lee Young) But where did you start from?
How do you explain it?
I was a bachelor from the beginning.
were living in the same house
It wasn't like that at first
Now like this...
Oh, I don't know, my head hurts so much, I won't do it.
When I find out later
Wouldn’t they be more upset?
Are we still friends?
We're not friends
They don't like me very much.
I don’t think so?
So do they
What if people at the hospital misunderstand?
I'm worried.
(Lee Young) It’s a mistake I always make.
It's a mistake I make every day
I'm preoccupied with dating
I'm afraid they'll say that
I sound like that
I hear it often and it’s okay.
I'm afraid they'll avoid me
To my brother
Yes?
uh?
why?
That's right
Dowon Oppa
[Exciting music]
No, that's right, in terms of age,
(Dowon) Yes...
Yes?
what is example
Say ‘yes’
Oh, not yet
No, in the hospital
Doing well with ‘Hey’, ‘You’, and ‘Oh I-young’?
Is that so?
Then what
(Dowon) Well...
This...
[Dowon’s light sigh]
Oh I-young
Teacher, I can’t do it, really!
(Lee Young) Let’s go home, bachelor in law.
Ugh
[Dowon’s sigh]
[TV sound]
[Message incoming sound]
[Sound of conversation between Jooyoung and Seungwon]
[Lee Young’s shy smile]
[mobile phone typing sound]
- (Jooyoung) Hey
- (Lee Young) Why?
(Jooyoung) Are you dating?
(Lee Young) Huh?
Oh, no?
uh
[light music]
- (Jooyoung, Seungwon) What?
- (Dowon) Yes?
(Seungwon) What!
(Jooyoung) I knew that would happen
I spent the whole day just listening to the phone.
Ah, indeed
(Seungwon) Hey, if you want to sit, sit down.
If it's going to turn off, turn it off
Who is it?
Are you from the hospital?
[Seungwon’s surprised gasp]
(Jooyoung) Oh my, did you know too?
(Dowon) No, yes?
uh? Ah...
(Seungwon) There’s no way he would know
Is he interested in anything like that?
Who is it?
(Jooyoung) Oh, it’s okay, I don’t know.
you don't date
- Why?
- (Jooyoung) Yes?
No, just looking at it, it looks like someone from a hospital.
We started dating again and broke up for no reason.
I'm afraid it might cause a fuss.
This is a really big pot.
It heated up so quickly.
How quickly it cools down
Ha, when me?
and sister
I've never been in a relationship
This is my first love
[Jooyoung snorts]
Wonwoo, Sangmin
(Jooyoung) And who else was it?
What is Huni Huni?
Well, what is Soni Soni?
Anyway, don’t you remember?
Oh, it's our first meeting.
Who is it, who is it?
Anyway, I'm going around saying I'm in a relationship
(Jooyoung) People who work
Don't make me uncomfortable
These are people you have to keep seeing for 4 years.
That's right
So, love at work, love with friends
A tangled love affair
They say that kind of thing is not good.
My brother-in-law is also in an office relationship, right?
(Seungwon) If you’re going to get married like us, you can do it.
Are you going to do it?
[Squirts water]
[Seungwon’s surprised groan]
(Jooyoung) Oh, my!
[humorous music]
[Dowon's cough]
Well, I'm not bean sprouts, I'm drinking water
(Seungwon) So dirty, Mr.
(Jooyoung) Ah, but what, what?
What are you doing?
marriage?
you?
[Sniffling sound]
(Jooyoung) Oh, really
Then I'm going to the hospital the day after tomorrow.
Just show it to me
Please at least say hello lightly
[Sound of trimming bean sprouts]
[Lee Young’s awkward laughter]
I was just kidding, I was just kidding.
Smile a little
[Throwing bean sprouts] Oh, really.
Hey
What nonsense are you talking about?
Do this seriously!
Why are you angry?
When do I!
(Lee Young) Ha, right
It's me and the bean sprouts that are easy!
Ah, why is this like this again?
[Sound of throwing bean sprouts]
My sister-in-law understands.
Because I have my third blood test the day after tomorrow.
It's because I'm nervous
(Jooyoung) What are you saying?
I'm fine, right?
what is tension
[Jooyoung sighs]
The results of the first blood test were ambiguous.
I did a second blood test.
It went up again vaguely
The 3rd is better than the 2nd
They say it needs to be twice as much, is that okay?
[Sound of throwing bean sprouts]
But the tester kept showing two lines.
(Jooyoung) It was like that during the third test tube.
It wasn't
don't expect anything
Okay, I don't have any expectations.
Hehe, I'm going to do it one more time, whatever.
Whatever happens, it's good
- If it doesn't work, there's nothing I can do.
- (Seungwon) Yes
Oh, by the way, I couldn't go to the hospital that day.
Just one of you please come
Let me do you a favor.
I'll check the time
What's going on, you look very busy?
Ah, based on nanoparticles
There is something I was researching.
It is said to be deterministic statistical optimization.
What...what does what?
It's called nanoparticles
The polymer coating that modifies the surface
Hey, there's something like that.
(Seungwon) Who started the research?
This is Senior Researcher Jooyoung Oh.
[Jooyoung sighs]
(Jooyoung) Until I quit
It was my research that I cherished.
[Sound of trimming bean sprouts]
[sigh]
While it goes on like this
what did i do
[Sound of throwing bean sprouts]
[Calm music]
No, I mean
Because I have my share in it too
Tell yourself to do better
Then, everything will be fine for me and you.
[light sigh]
Don't expect anything
Okay
[Sound of trimming bean sprouts]
[Sound of throwing bean sprouts]
[Jooyoung’s light sigh]
[Newborn baby cries]
[Sound of door opening]
- (Lee Young) Oh, I'll write it!
- (Namkyung) I’ll write it, I’ll write it
I'll write it
(Lee Young) I am the mother of Professor Seo Jeong-min.
(Namkyung) Oh, just stay still.
That, Professor Gong Gong-seon
(Mugang) Quiet, babies wake up.
[Moo-gang laughs]
'Cause I'm okay with anything
Let us both come to an agreement and let you know.
We fight all the time, all the time, ugh
[Nanjing’s sigh]
[light music]
(Nanjing) Prieclamsia Road
Na Hyo-jin, a 33-week-old mother in the MFICU
I've been playing BP stable for a while.
It rose to the 150s starting this morning.
Complaining of headache
I think we need to take the baby out today.
(Lee Young) To PP ROM
Chae Yu-ra, a 33-week-old mother in the MFICU
I started having a fever in the morning
I have to take the baby out today.
EBW is only 1,900g
(Namkyung) [surprised] Really?
My baby weighs 1,800g?
Smaller and more delicate
(Lee Young) My mother
Suspected chorioamnionitis
(Nanjing) Our mother may develop eclampsia.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
- Oh, you send the power.
- (Lee Young) I said no.
(Namkyung) I can’t either.
- (Pause) Yes, this is pediatrics.
- (Namkyung) If you are going to send all the pregnant women,
- I want to go with you.
- (Mugang) Yes, I will go right away.
(Lee Young) Go, then you
[Nanjing’s muttering]
- Why is that?
- (Namkyung) Uh, where are you going?
(Mugang) Myung-won Myung-won is in labor.
Suddenly the baby is not doing well
Get out of the way
Take care of your feet
[Nanjing’s sigh]
(Lee Young) Mr. I, there is no such thing as a sharp robber, tsk.
[Sound of door closing]
(Tattoo Man) Would you like me to come and take a look?
My mom's injections are leaking again, again.
Oh, yes, I understand.
[Sound of the tattooed man clicking his tongue]
thank you
(Jaeil) No, I told my mother the other day.
They said I was injected twice
Aren't you the guardian who cursed and caused a fuss?
yes, that's right
Why are you even saying thank you?
(Juyeon) Ah!
Well, when I was last hospitalized
I saw you call me lady
The professor exploded with anger.
Be kind after that.
That's just the way he speaks
- I'll go and take a look.
- (Grassland) Yes
(Junmo) Hey, what did you do?
The patient is so feverish?
(Meadow) Ah...
Like that
Because it’s day 1 of POD
Chest x-ray was performed
There were no special findings, so I made an observation.
Even if there is no problem there
If the patient has repeated fever
Shouldn’t we do something?
Blood culture and ravaged culture
It's done on the 2nd to 3rd day of POD.
Wound Culture until the 4th and 5th days of POD
This is done when you have a fever?
(Sabi) Still, I cry
When dressing for tomorrow's routine
I tried to check
Hey
Are you teaching me now?
no
(Junmo) Did I tell you?
Tell me only what I don't know
Don't explain everything you know!
sorry
(Junmo) The POD has lasted for a few days and is nagging.
the patient has a fever
Shouldn’t we find the cause?
So what should I do?
I don't know?
I know
But why aren't you answering?
Tell the professor what you don't know...
Ha, are you kidding, really...
[Junmo’s sigh]
Whether it's blood culture or ravaging culture
Checking for sound complications
patient right away
Work up your fever to make sure you don’t have a fever.
Got it?
(Sabi) Yes, I understand.
I guess it was obstetrics.
You must have done things so sloppily, tsk
[sigh]
(Japan) Oh!
No, why are we talking about obstetrics here?
(Sabi) I don’t know
Last time, on day 1 of POD
what test
I asked if you do that much
What should you do with me?
Write, I see
It seems like you were photographed in a big way.
What did you do wrong?
I?
No, nothing at all
(Jay) Um...
Sabiya
Yes, this is a method I often use.
[Soft music]
The professor's expression is bad.
It's so serious
Then hit the player first
Sorry! Like this
(Sabi) I didn’t do anything wrong
Why do you say sorry?
Oh, just
Just say you're sorry and do it.
I don't have anything to apologize for, so what can I say?
Ah, so...
[Jaeil’s sigh]
Okay, okay.
do whatever you want
Hey, I'm going to surgery.
In the meantime, don't get scolded.
(Residence in Japan) Ugh
Hey, because I live
Am I telling you all these things?
[light laughter]
[Medical device operation sound]
(Japan) But, Professor
Why not open surgery for this cancer surgery?
Do you do it like this?
Oh, I'm not saying it's wrong.
So, it's a complicated surgery.
Why laparoscopy instead of open surgery?
I'm curious
It's not an argument, it's just a question.
It's real
(Jaehwi) Wow, I’m a little touched right now.
No, it's been a year
The question you asked me during surgery
This is my first time
oh
Everyone just
I guess so, I guess that's right
The professor says he will take care of it.
Who cares about such things?
hmm!
According to the results of the study, whether laparoscopy or open surgery
There is no difference in patient outcome.
But in the case of this patient
You are old.
So now as much as possible
I'm thinking of shortening the surgery time.
How did you get the answer to your question?
Teacher Taejin Yoon?
(Eunmi) Eom Jae-il
(Jaehwi) Uh, yes, yes
Ah, ah, Eom Jae-il, Eom Jae-il
Uh, yeah, you know.
No, that's it.
You know, I did that again, that...
Ha, ha, hi man
(Japan) Hi Boys
[Eunmi’s laughter]
(Jaehwi) I’m sorry
Sorry, boy
[Eunmi and Jaehwi’s laughter]
I'll take out the sample.
[Jaehwi sighs]
[ECG meter beeping sound]
Something like this, huh?
Why does this happen?
Make people cry like that, tsk
I don't know if it hurts
[Jaehwi sighs]
Anyway
hi boys
[Eunmi and Jaeil’s laughter]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Mouse operation sound]
(Myungseon) Are you really not going?
Professor Gong Gong-seon shoots pizza
Is this really rare?
He said he ordered it at a really good restaurant.
I don't like that pizza very much.
Last time we played one...
Ah!
[Awkward laughter]
(Lee Young) I like it
Today...
Did you pretend?
- Would you like some medicine?
- (Lee Young) No, no!
[Awkward laughter]
It's okay
(Lee Young) I don’t take my medicine well.
Come back
Then we will eat quickly and come back.
No way
Can't you?
Please come slowly
(Lee Young) Eat a lot and chew thoroughly.
Because I can pretend
(Myungseon) Ah
- (Jiyoung) Yes, let’s eat quickly.
- (Myungseon) I will eat and come back.
(Jiyoung) It sounds delicious.
[Myeongseon’s happy laughter]
[Exciting music]
(Do-won) Oh, come back after eating pizza.
I like this better
[Sound of chopsticks dropping]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
Teacher Oh I-young
I'm saying that because I'm really confused.
Do you want to keep it a secret?
Do you want to start a rumor?
I don't know
(Lee Young) But I want to be with you
I'm sure
[Dowon’s embarrassed laughter]
me too
[Embarrassed laughter]
[Dowon clears his throat]
[Lee Young’s laughter]
(Dowon) I can’t quite grasp it.
Meat too
- (Lee Young) Meat too?
- (Dowon) Yes
What about spinach?
- Spinach too?
- (Dowon) Yes
I'm so tired I don't even have the strength to lift a spoon.
Oh, I guess I'll have to do it.
No, Teacher Oh I-young, no...
- (Lee Young) Oh, I’m strong.
- (Dowon) Oh, are you really okay?
Ah
Shuung
[Sound of door opening]
[Music stops]
(Dowon) Oh, real chopsticks!
If you drop it, pick it up...
Huh? Hello, Teacher Myeong-won?
- Yes, ah, Teacher Oh I-young.
- Yes
(Eunwon) I heard the front surgery will take a bit longer.
Leave the mother 30 minutes late
yes
[Sound of coffee pot water boiling]
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Eunwon) Yes, professor.
The letter of recommendation was written by Professor Kong Gong-seon.
[Sound of pouring water]
Ah
Professor applications are due next week.
I'll organize it a little more.
yes
yes, thank you
[Call end sound]
Sseu-eup, over there, Mr. Gu Do-won
Are you a professor applicant this time?
Have you heard how many people there are?
no
Ah, I heard that Teacher Yoo Jeong-hye published it.
Oh, him?
But that's a lunch box
(Eunwon) Yes
Eat deliciously
[Awkward laughter]
See you later
(Dowon) Yes
[Lee Young and Dowon sigh]
be surprised
[Lee Young sighs in relief]
This damn hospital is so big.
I have nowhere to go on a date
Because dates are usually held outside.
I go back and forth between the hospital and home all the time.
When, where, and how do you do it?
(Lee Young) And we
There are two eyes at home too.
That's right
Oh, I have to go to work this weekend too.
Ah, sir!
Well then, shall we meet on the fire escape later tonight?
-There aren't many people there...
- (Dowon) Umm
Every floor is already full.
(Lee Young), you don’t do what you’re told to do.
Then an elevator?
[laughter]
Oh I-young, I watched too many movies.
Would that work?
Oh, then where can I see it?
me after 9 o'clock
I think I'll have about 30 minutes.
Let's have some coffee there.
There won't be anyone there
Where is it?
There
[cell phone ringing sound]
Oh, sir, you don’t even notice anything.
Why?
[Ultrasound device button sound]
(Nanjing) Mother, the length of the cervix is fine.
It's all good
Now you can go up to the ward.
yes, thank you
I have to start an outpatient ultrasound now.
Come out quickly
I'll see just one more person, really the last time
No way
Can’t you see there are a lot of pregnant women outside?
- I'll see you soon.
- (Lee Young) I can’t do it.
In the ward, maternity ward
Just look at the portable ultrasound.
Why did you come down to the ultrasound room?
Professor Gong Gong-seon
I told you to look at the official Sonoro.
Oh, I don't know.
sorry
(Lee Young) Come out
[Interesting music]
(Lee Young) If the ultrasound is delayed, the outpatient clinic will be pushed back.
(Nankyung) No, I know too.
Making a decision in a hurry
They say everything, even the Doppler, is viewed as official.
What should I do then?
ah!
It's no big deal
(Nanjing) If you sit there for a moment
I'll come pick you up right away.
(Mother 1) Yes
Then come and see me during lunch break during the outpatient break.
How many times do I say I just heard that too?
Hey, please, just this once, okay?
I need to see you quickly and go up to the ward.
Ah, sir...
Then quickly
[cell phone ringing sound]
Yes, professor
(Jeongmin) Is Moon Cha-seon’s maternal ultrasound still available?
Why don't you come over to the outpatient department?
Oh, sorry.
The ultrasound is a bit delayed.
I will see you right away and send you to an outpatient clinic right away.
(Jeongmin) Oh Iyoung
Because of ultrasound
Outcalls have been disconnected since the morning.
How can I go?
no, sorry
(Lee Young) See you soon
[cell phone ringing sound]
Yes, professor
Oh, I saw it all.
That one person seems a bit difficult...
No, you can
yes
Yes, I understand, yes.
[Call end tone]
[Nanjing’s sigh]
(Namkyung) Hey, Oiyoung, just this once!
(Junmo) Hello?
- (Jaehwi) Hello?
- (Jae-il) Hello?
- (Jae-il) Hello, how are you?
(Jaehwi) Hello?
Ah, here it is
(Junmo) Aig, without that hair cut
You have to prepare in advance
Why run, run, tsk
[Jaehwi’s speaking voice]
Uh, uh, huh?
Oh, what are you doing now?
[Sound of chopsticks falling]
Ah, hot, ah, ah!
[Junmo’s hot breathing]
[Junmo’s sigh]
Patient Jeon Mi-yeon is having her first surgery tomorrow.
Do you know about ostomy surgery for intestinal obstruction?
I know
(Junmo) But why is it on the fasting patient table?
Do you have any porridge?
What are you doing to avoid surgery? uh?
That...
(Junmo) I personally told the chief of surgery
It's a surgery I asked for.
If it's canceled
Will I sell it or not?
It's co-op...
Collaborating with surgeons...
(Junmo) So?
Oh, so what?
prescription
surgical resident
(Junmo) Why him?
Oh, what is he!
sorry
(Junmo) Hey
Are you coming to the hospital to save someone?
Or are you coming to kill me?
It's a shame because I was making rounds at the time.
What would have happened otherwise?
(Chief of Surgery) Professor Joonmo Cho
Uh hey
(Jun’s mother) Hey, Chief.
No, I can't call.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I am now...
Because of my major
Oh, by the way, what's going on?
Uh, um, ah...
Hey, our resident made a mistake?
(Chief of Surgery) I confused the patient.
Patient Jeon Mi-yeon
He said he prescribed a diet.
Ah, well, that's how the ceremony goes...
[Embarrassed laughter]
Ah, so
You mean that porridge, porridge, yes?
(Chief of Surgery) Uh, uh
That, that porridge
Have you eaten that already?
No, you didn't eat it.
(Chief of Surgery) Oh my...
(Junmo) Oh, what?
Are you worried about that?
I'm double checking everything.
Anyway, I'm glad, I'm glad
(Chief of Surgery) You are real
(Surgical resident) I’m sorry.
sorry
No
That happens often.
Uh, it's okay, yeah
- (Chief of Surgery) Be careful from now on, okay?
- (Surgical resident) Yes.
Sseu-eup, manager, you came and went.
Why don’t you at least have some tea?
Oh, I guess so, then?
- Okay, let's go.
- (Junmo) Yes
(Chief of Surgery) You go quickly and see.
[Junmo’s light smile]
[sigh]
don't speak
I'm not like that
(Sabi) Because I’m scared...
The professor was wrong.
(Jaehwi) Teacher Kim Sa-bi, there is nothing wrong
So spread your shoulders
yes
(Jaehwi) Cheer up
Fighting...
Don't just say this
I need some help.
[Calm music]
Oh, it's okay, thank you
I'll give the patient a prescription so go
Come and have a cup of coffee
(Sabi) No.
(Jaehwi) No, no.
Come back, I, I said I wanted to drink.
Come on, hurry up, come back
Wake up, wake up, quickly, quickly, quickly
Now go and get mine
You know, that aaro
You know what something like this is, right?
Let's see, let's see
[Mouse operation sound]
What is this? Let's see.
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Nanjing’s sigh]
[Nanjing’s deep sigh]
Aren’t you guys hungry?
[Sharp sound effect]
[humorous music]
[Angry cat crying sound effect]
What about you?
[Sound effect of broken program operation]
Why?
(Jaeil) What’s in your coffee?
Does it taste weird?
no
[Makes a yuck sound]
(Jae-il) Today, there was pork served in the cafeteria.
- (Lee Young) Really? Then
- (Namkyung) Hey, Eom Jae-il
Today is the day we eat snacks, right?
Ask what the snacks are like
To whom?
Eom Jae-il
I ate snacks yesterday
I ate meat yesterday
Then tonight
- Jeyuk
- Snacks
[Lee Young sighs]
(Residence in Japan) The two of us decide
Why do you keep doing this to me?
Did you guys fight?
- (together) No!
- (Sabi) We fought
(Lee Young) What are you fighting for?
Why fight with him?
yes
There's no need to fight with him
Even though I get scolded a lot because of him
[absurd laughter]
who will say anything
Hey Sabi
(Nanjing) There was an urgent mother in the ward.
A quick look before an outpatient ultrasound
Is that such a big deal?
(Lee Young) Hey, Eom Jae-il
I still have foreign processes
There's a kid who doesn't understand
So surprising?
[Nanjing’s amazing exclamation]
[Jaeil’s sigh]
I'm just saying let's have dinner
[Dog whining sound effect]
[Program operation sound effect]
[Jaeil’s sigh]
Done
Let's not eat, uh
Let’s all starve together!
hey! Why eat it!
Professor Jaehwi Ryu bought it for me!
Oh, I'm sorry!
[humorous music]
[Jae-il’s amazing exclamation]
Oh really you guys
(Japan) Is this something that needs to be done like this?
[depressing music]
With something that's nothing, Mr. Real
Ah, Mr.
I'm going, Mr.
You guys don't catch me
I'm really going
Mr...
[Sound of door opening and closing]
(Infertility nurse) Thank you for your hard work.
I'll contact you as soon as the results come out.
It will take about an hour
Well, there are no more blood tests anymore, right?
Is this the last time?
Probably so
Maybe
So what happens next?
(Infertility nurse) Ah...
If the numbers come out good
They'll ask for an ultrasound next week.
ultrasonic side
You're taking pictures of the baby's house, right?
(Infertility nurse) Yes
(Jooyoung) In 1 hour
Are you calling me at 1:30?
As soon as the results come out
I'll contact you as soon as possible
yes, thank you
(Jeongmin) Oh Iyoung
There are many new patients tomorrow.
Also, make an outpatient ultrasound delay?
uh?
(Lee Young) Yes
no, no
(Kiseon) When there is an ultrasonic delay,
Complaints are no joke
Namkyung Pyo
I am a mother who will see an outpatient ultrasound tomorrow.
About 25 people?
(Namkyung) Uh, yes
(Kiseon) I will go to the hospital tomorrow
It has to end at 5 o'clock
There is absolutely no delay, okay?
(Nanjing) I’ll see you as soon as possible.
(Jeongmin) And in the obstetrics ward
I heard there's a hospital room.
(Kiseon) I have to write that
(Jeongmin) That’s what I was trying to say now.
[Interesting music]
I have to write it
(Kiseon) My mother in the gynecological ward.
I have to get off
It's hard to make rounds
Do you know what I mean, Mr. Pyo Nam-kyung?
(Nanjing) Yes
That's what I said
(Jeongmin) My mother too
Are you in the gynecological ward? Please
Take care and eat
yes
[Call connection tone]
(Namkyung) Yes, it’s the administrative department, right?
My name is Pyo Nam-kyung, an obstetrics and gynecology major.
Yes, ah, in that obstetric ward.
Just because I got a seat
(Lee Young) Hey!
Sorry, I have work to do.
(Jooyoung) Do what you do, it doesn’t suit you
Have you called yet?
(Jooyoung) Oh
[Jooyoung sighs nervously]
Are you nervous?
no
If it was going to work, it would have happened in the first blood test.
Tsk, I’m not looking forward to it.
[cell phone ringing sound]
yes
Yes, Oh Joo-young.
(Jooyoung) Ah...
[light laughter]
Ah, yes
thank you
yes
[Call end sound]
What is the number?
It was 153 in the second round, but it fell further.
Chemical miscarriage?
How did you know?
[Jooyoung’s empty laughter]
That's right, you're a doctor.
(Lee Young) Are you laughing?
(Jooyoung) Is it because you didn’t have any expectations?
What more than thinking
I don't really feel bad
[Sad music]
It's okay
Did I hear the baby's heartbeat?
What did you feel like the baby was moving?
One cell is missing, okay?
and
God has two embryos left
It's okay, you can do it again, yeah
(Lee Young) Let’s eat and go, I have some time.
(Jooyoung) I’m busy, but the food is ready.
Buy me a cup of coffee
In the meantime, I'm doing a test tube.
I couldn't drink as much coffee as I wanted
I want to have a refreshing drink
Go, then
[Coffee machine operating sound]
What about you?
(Lee Young) Ah
I'm having a glass of iced Americano.
Please give me an iced latte.
Oh, the iced latte is decaffeinated...
(Jooyoung) Ah...
No
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
I guess it just became a habit
[Jooyoung’s light smile]
[Weeping sigh]
Doing useless things
I worked hard too
[Jooyoung’s crying]
(Lee Young) Hey, a little
[Lee Young clears his throat awkwardly]
sorry
A glass of iced Americano
[Jooyoung’s crying]
[Lee Young clears his throat]
Add iced cafe latte shot
- Please give me a lot of caffeine.
- (Clerk) Yes.
[Monitor operation sound]
[sniffling sound]
[Coffee machine operating sound]
[Clears cough]
[cell phone ringing sound]
[Mobile phone ringing sound - continued]
(Jaeil) Hello, Professor.
Oh, Sabi Kim went to the bathroom for a moment.
Yes, we will check and contact you right away.
yes
[Counter operating sound]
[Call end sound]
[Jaeil makes a yuck sound]
It's no big deal
Check operating room schedule
(Sabi) Ah...
[Calm music]
Have you eaten?
(Japan) Then let’s go to a restaurant.
why?
Do you want to meet the professor?
Why did you come?
Why would you come to the bank?
Come to get money
Close the door here now, let's go
(Sabi) Yes
(Japan) I want to be alone
I come here during the day
Go there at night
Where?
No one is coming
It's quiet
[Laughter leaking out]
(Ikjun) Don't laugh, ah, be quiet
[Jeongmin’s laughter]
(Emergency resident) Please excuse me.
[Soft music]
I'll see, my friend.
(Emergency resident) Oh, yes.
- (Jeongmin) Thank you
- (Emergency resident) Yes, I understand.
[Jeongmin holding back laughter]
[sigh]
It was very difficult for me to get here.
Please take a good look
Okay
Okay, so stop asking.
What do friends ask for so earnestly?
Oh, I told you not to laugh
(Ikjun) I’m going crazy, really.
[Jeongmin’s laughter leaks out]
[sigh]
(Jeongmin) No, what should I do?
Is this what happens?
[lively music]
There was a bond on the desk
But I don't know
I elbowed Bond.
So what happens?
The bond will flow, right?
(Jeongmin) Oh
(Ikjun) I don’t want to spill that.
I quickly received it with my hand.
This is what happened
If your hand breaks, you will be unemployed.
I'm unemployed
So, Jeong Man-ah
(Ikjun) Please
[Jeongmin’s laughter leaks out]
Amen, Namaste
It’s Sawaadi Kab, really, huh?
[Message incoming sound]
(Jeongmin) Huh?
(Ikjun) Oh, it’s over here.
[Jeongmin sighs]
[Jeongmin’s laughter leaks out]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Hey, no, face recognition
Oh, that's it, wait a minute.
Ah, Mr.
Wow, so many different things...
[Jeongmin’s laughter]
(Ikjun) IC, typo
That's it, that's done!
Oh, put it back
[Ikjun sighs]
(Jeongmin) Give it to me
Hey, but can an obstetrician take a look at this?
(Ikjun) Oh
Oh, that's right, there's a specialist in this.
We're in the hospital now.
Where, dermatologist?
Orthopedic? Oh, direct transfer?
Not there
(Ikjun) Oh, don’t do that, you do it.
I will help you
Professor, please do the surgery.
No, if you have an accident, go to your hospital.
Why did you come here and make a fuss?
This is close to my house
Let's do it like that.
I didn’t go because I was embarrassed.
[Message incoming sound]
[Ikjun sighs]
(Jeongmin) Huh?
Come, specialist.
Oh, who is it?
Is this someone I know?
There is no one who can come after me in this field.
My name is
(Songhwa) Lee Ikjun?
[surprised gasp]
[Music: ‘Wise Doctor Life’ OST]
You said you'd meet me at the camping site later.
Why are you here?
What are the hands again?
What did you do?
Bond...
I buried it
Why Bond?
Oh, you have your favorite camping lantern.
The hand hook fell off and I was trying to attach it.
(Songhwa) Ah, really!
I told you to leave it alone
- (Ikjun) Write, ah!
- (Songhwa) Look
[Ikjun’s painful exclamation]
Does it hurt a lot?
[Ikjun's painful breathing]
Hey, what should I do with my hands?
[Jeongmin’s laughter leaks out]
(Ikjun) Songhwa, why are you here?
I said I finished organizing my thesis today.
Chihong is late with the data.
I'm here to help
How did you know Songhwa was here?
Songhwa said she had some business to run here.
We had lunch together and went up to the lab.
I got a call right away saying you were in the emergency room.
Minah Jeong
How should I do this?
(Jeongmin) Let’s try it with the warm cell line first.
If that doesn't work, I'll have to call an orthopedic surgeon and have it cut.
Hey, this guy
You are having a hard time too.
(Kiseon) Ikjuna
(Ikjun) Huh? who is this?
Ikjuna
Oh my, what's going on with you?
Jeongmin said you came to the emergency room.
how surprised i was
[Kiseon’s surprised gasp]
No, it's because he
Are you calling me while I'm in the lab?
(Ikjun) Hi, kong
How have you been, Jun?
(Ikjun) Ah, then, yes.
[Sigh of the steamer]
(Kiseon) Are you okay?
How did this happen?
(Ikjun) So this is
[Ikjun sighs]
(Jeongmin) You
Do you think you only see one person?
[Surprise] Oh my, Songhwa!
[Songhwa’s laughter]
(Kiseon) It’s been so long
[Ikjun laughs]
how have you been doing?
Oh, how have you become prettier?
no
[Songhwa’s shy smile]
(Ikjun) So
Songhwa becomes prettier every day
(Songhwa) It’s been a really long time since Kiseon
You haven't changed from 3 years ago.
[Kiseon’s embarrassed laughter]
(Jeongmin) Oh, it’s the same, both the face and the skills are all the same.
(Ikjun) Songhwa, look at this.
Oh, I'm really going crazy
[Soft music]
It stings
- (Songhwa) Does it sting a lot?
- (Ikjun) It’s not a stinging level.
head
(Songhwa) Ah, now!
Mind my mind, mind yours!
What should I do?
Don't try to force it off.
- (Ikjun) I didn’t take it off, but this is still...
- What?
Didn't you know?
[Songhwa’s laughter]
You are in your last love with your first love, Songhwa.
(Jeongmin) It’s been a while.
- You didn't know?
- (Songhwa) Don’t play around, please.
Oh, so?
[Awkward laughter]
No, I knew that too, right?
(Songhwa) Camping is prohibited for the time being.
Here, here?
(Ikjun) Ah! It hurts there
So wipe off your lipstick and tell me
[Sound of Ik-jun and Song-hwa talking]
(Songhwa) Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham
[Songhwa’s laughter]
(Ikjun) IC
[Kiseon’s heartbreaking elasticity]
Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham Cham
[Ikjun and Songhwa’s laughter]
(Songhwa) I, I won
- Me, hahahaha!
- (Ikjun) Ah, hey, it’s a foul.
- If you hit me like that.
- (Songhwa) What, uh, oh, I overdid it.
Didn't you hit me too hard?
(Ikjun) No, it’s okay
- No, he wants me to take it off quickly. Now.
- (Songhwa) Sorry, sorry, sorry
(Junmo) Aig, Aig
The previous surgery took a long time
What if my surgery is going to be delayed?
Take care of another room
Shouldn’t you find out?
No, I couldn't even find an operating room.
Why are you here and why do you get paid?
why?
Because it’s not an obstetrics department.
Not interested in surgery?
Hey there
(Junmo) Or because it’s not an obstetrics department.
There's no need to be good at it, right?
Not an OBGY, but you
So you're at OB, huh?
Manager!
[Sound of putting pen down]
[Jaehwi sighs]
(Jaehwi) You want to scold me
Just talk about the operating room, the rest.
More useless words
I don't think you need to attach it.
No...
Professor Jaehwi Ryu, to whom now...
Professor!
To the professor
This is what I am saying
(Jaehwi) If you do something wrong
Of course I have to scold him.
But
[sigh]
Even in places or sentences where you are scolded
Because courtesy is necessary, right?
(Junmo) Professor Ryu
Courtesy is that you are not there now, you are
[humorous music]
[Sabi’s sobbing sound]
no
Am I doing this for no reason?
uh?
This is all too
It's discipline and education, you idiot.
Where is the gentleman here now!
(Jaehwi) And
Questions like why do you get paid?
I'm guessing it's because it's not an obstetrics department!
Wherever you look, it’s education and discipline!
Teacher Sabi Kim
[Sabi’s sobbing sound]
What did he do wrong?
I think you get it all, right?
[Sabi’s whimpering sound]
Stop it now, Professor.
Yeah, yeah
I tried to stop too
Ah, but why are you so angry?
Is the atmosphere here getting rough? Wow
(Junmo) Okay, I’m sorry.
Sorry, uh, sorry.
Oh, it's no big deal.
Look at things, uh, yeah, yeah
[Jaeil’s sigh]
[Calm music]
Ah, Mr. Sabi Kim.
But you
Did you get an apology?
(Jaehwi) I forgot that, I
(Sabi) Professor
You did it
I think I heard an apology
thank you
[Jaehwi sighs]
Then I'm glad
Ah, but that's really what my senior said.
There are kids too.
[Junmo’s surprised exclamation]
(Junmo) Oh, what is it, Mr.
sorry
You're not hurt anywhere, are you?
I'm a professor here, yeah
(Tattooed Man) But?
[light music]
There are a lot of sick people here
Let's be careful
yes
sorry
[Humorous sound effects]
(Tattooed Man) I... I didn’t swear, did I?
(Jaehwi) Ah
[Jaehwi’s laughter]
I just now
Don't make any noise in the hospital.
Well, I don't speak informally to anyone, yeah
Oh, good job, good job
That's why you're smiling like this
How good does it look?
(Jaehwi) Since you’re smiling like this, it’s a little bit
You're so cute
Me?
[Jaehwi and Moon Moon-nam’s laughter]
Ah, uh, where are you going?
Ah, in the ward
I heard your mother has improved a lot?
Test numbers are also improving?
It's thanks to the professor.
(Jaehwi) Oh my, because you smile like this
You're getting better.
[Tattoo Man’s Laughter]
(Jaehwi) I understand
[Jaehwi’s laughter]
Always smiling like that, yeah
(Tattoo Man) Yes
[Jaehwi’s laughter]
- Come in!
- (Jaehwi) Yes
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Lee Young yawns]
[Mouse operation sound]
[Keyboard operation sound]
(Dowon) Pyo Nam-kyung
- Yes?
- (Do-won) and Oh I-young
you guys
Are you competing to see who is worse?
Both of them postponed the charting as scheduled.
Oh I-young
Birth certificate, delivery discharge
Discharge summary for mothers scheduled to be discharged tomorrow
I heard you didn’t write it all down?
And you, Pyo Nam-kyung
Patients scheduled for surgery next week
I haven't recorded any hospitalization records.
Why don’t you identify the patient in advance, huh?
sorry
(Dowon) I went into surgery and will come back.
In the meantime, I organized everything
Show it to me and get off work.
Okay?
I will check everything one by one
(together) yes
[Lee Young sighs]
[telephone ringing sound]
yes
Yes?
(Namkyung) Ah, yes, yes
I'll tell the professor right away.
yes
[Sound of putting down receiver]
[Sound of helicopter flying]
[nervous music]
(Medical staff 1) Mother
Come to your senses, mother?
(Medical staff 2) Hemoglobin is 6.6.
(Medical staff 1) My blood pressure keeps dropping?
- Please squeeze the blood harder.
- (Medical staff 2) Yes
(Medical staff 1) Mother
Mom, open your eyes
Please tell me the name of the mother.
maternal body
[Sound of the captain radioing]
(Medical staff 2) Mother
- I'm moving, I'm moving
- (Medical Staff 1) Please listen!
- (Junseok) One, two, three!
- (Medical Staff 1) One, two, three!
(Together) One, two, three!
(Medical staff 1) 2 hours ago
I gave birth through rapid labor.
Balloon insertion was performed with PPH.
Bleeding continues
BP dropped from 70 to 40
Currently it's 60 out of 90.
Blood transfusion is the first pack of Universal O.
I had DDLT surgery 7 years ago.
[Nanjing’s surprised exclamation]
Ah, the new mother!
(Namkyung) Oh, mother, come to your senses!
Mother!
(Junseok) First, stop by the ER.
Secure the line first
I think it would be better to upload an operating room.
Connect the patient monitor
I'll check your vitals.
- (Emergency Nurse 1) Yes
- (Junseok) Please bring me an ultrasound.
(Emergency Nurse 2) Yes
[Nervous music - continued]
[shaking breathing]
- (Junseok) I’ll take the C line.
- (Emergency Nurse 3) Yes
[The electrocardiograph beeps rapidly]
[shaking breathing]
(Lee Young) Pyo Nam-kyung
[Sound of blood flowing]
Namkyung Pyo
- Hey, Pyo Nam-kyung!
- (Namkyung) Huh?
[Nankyung’s trembling breathing]
Youngah Lee
Let's do this quickly...
Oh, I don't think I can do it
I don't know
What do you not know?
It's bleeding
- Hey!
- (Namkyung) Huh?
(Lee Young) The mother said she was bleeding
(Nanjing) Uh
If you bleed, uh, recognize it quickly.
Ah, quickly...
- Just hold the line.
- (Emergency Nurse 3) Yes
Because I paid for the speed CP
(Lee Young) Uh...
Teacher!
(Lee Young) Please insert the poly.
Then uh...
Uh, please give me the oxytocin fluid mix.
Please give me a carbetocin IV shot.
yes
(Emergency resident) Are you going to the lab?
(Emergency Nurse 3) Yes, I’m leaving.
Sir, Rapid Infusion System
Please
yes
Please give me a fluid full drip
(Emergency Nurse 3) Yes, I understand.
opened
(Lee Young) Pyo Nam-kyung
[Nankyung’s trembling breathing]
Oh, come to your senses!
[Nervous music - continued]
I'm scared too
(Namkyung) Huh? Uh, uh
Remove the balloon first
-Operating room
- (Nankyung) Uh, uh
[Call connection tone]
Uh, obstetrics.
Is the operating room ready?
Oh, hurry, it's urgent, now.
[Call end sound]
- (Namkyung) Ah, teacher
- (Emergency Nurse 4) Yes
I contacted the (Nanjing) blood bank.
Uh, first, get two packs of Universal O.
- Please take me straight to the operating room.
- (Emergency Nurse 4) Yes
- (Nanjing) Quickly!
Teacher, please hold the A line too.
(Junseok) Yes
teacher
- (Namkyung) Yes?
- The mother has a history of DDLT.
Yes?
(Namkyung) Oh, that’s right
(Emergency Nurse 5) Lab results from the liver transplant team
I think we should get it together, but it hasn’t arrived yet.
(Ikjun) Give it to me, I’ll look at it.
[dark music]
yes
Ah, this is the liver of Yulje Headquarters.
- (Emergency Nurse 5) Ah...
- (Ikjun) Please
How long has it been since this patient's liver transplant surgery?
(Nanjing) Uh, it’s been 7 years.
I have a history of giving birth 2 years ago
Liver levels are normal, yes.
Use antibiotics like the general public.
I think I can go into surgery now.
Oh, because there can be adhesion.
Please be careful.
Hurry now
(Lee Young) Thank you
(Nanjing) Thank you
(Lee Young) I’ll upload it now
(Nanjing) I’m leaving the bed, please get out of the way!
[Urgent music]
[Ikjun sighs]
Uh, mother, calm down.
Oh, please!
(Mother 2) I’m so sleepy.
No, you can't sleep, open your eyes!
(Namkyung) Ah, the mother!
(Lee Young) Mother!
[Nankyung’s trembling breathing]
It's your baby's birthday today, right?
The baby is waiting for his mom because it’s his birthday.
We should go there
(Mother 2) Yes...
[Namkyung’s crying]
(Sanghyun) Please give me medicine.
(Anesthesia resident) Yes, I understand.
(Jeongmin) Isn’t it multi-tasting for new mothers?
(Lee Young) Yes, it’s multi.
(Nanjing) Delivery is two and a half hours ago.
The baby said it was okay.
(Jeongmin) How much bleeding?
(Lee Young) Uh, until now
I think it will be around 2,000cc.
When I saw the speculum in the emergency room
It was active bleeding.
(Jeongmin) How much blood went into it?
(Lee Young) I brought one from the helicopter.
This is the third time in total so far.
Two Universal O's were pre-loaded.
10 RBCs in blood bank
Uh, I prepared 5 FFPs.
(Jeongmin) When will it be ready?
(Lee Young) It will take about 20 minutes.
(Jeongmin) Did the CBC and DIC lab results come out?
[dark music]
(Namkyung) Yes, the rap that came out of the emergency room
CBC 6.2, uh, PLT 90,000
OTPT is normal
PT and aPTT
It is said to show signs of prolongation.
Ah, the other DIC lab
They say testing is in progress.
(Jeongmin) Well done, very good
Pyo Nam-kyung: Scrub first.
[Namkyung’s crying]
(Namkyung) I can’t do it...
[Jeongmin sighs]
(Jeongmin) Then Lee Young, you
[Lee Young’s heavy breathing]
How are you guys, don't lose your mind!
Mother now...
(Kiseon) You guys come out
(Jeongmin) What about surgery?
(Kisen) It’s over.
(Namkyung) Professor, I’m giving birth.
(Kisun) I know, you’re watching it now.
(Jeongmin) Hey, there is no weather today.
(Kisun) I guess so?
The only ones I can trust are our teachers
[ECG alarm sound]
(Anesthesiology resident) Blood pressure drops
It's 40 out of 70.
(Sanghyun) I’ll keep up with the volume
Don't worry, get started
(Jeongmin) Yes, let’s begin.
[Lee Young’s trembling breathing]
[ECG meter beeping sound]
[Medical device operation sound]
(Steamboat) Kelly
[Calm music]
- One more Kelly
- (Yunjeong) Yes
(Steamboat) Metgem
Sucheo Tai Won-o Preparation
(Jeongmin) Thai
(steamer) cut
(Jeongmin) Please give me tranexamic acid.
(Sanghyun) Yes, I understand.
(Jeongmin) Tonsil
Right angle
Grab the suction
- (Lee Young) Yes
- (Nanjing) Yes
[Dowon sighs in relief]
(Jeongmin) He underwent liver transplant surgery.
I was worried that the adhesion would be severe, but it was easy.
(Kisun) So, I’m glad.
(Jeongmin) What do you think?
(Lee Young) I don’t bleed
(Steamboat) And?
(Lee Young) Mother...
lived
(Nanjing) Mother’s Day
I can meet the baby
(Jeongmin) Not like that!
Blood loss is 4,000cc.
Maternal vitals are stable.
(Lee Young) Ah!
Yes, that's right, it's normal.
(Nankyung) The surgery went really well.
[Nankyung’s embarrassed laughter]
[Calm music]
[Kiseon snorts]
(Jeongmin) Hey
(Kisun) Why?
Write down the surgery report
Why do I use it, I have kids.
What will they remember?
I barely caught the runaway soul.
Ah, then you write it
You came first
It was originally written by Eosi!
I was a surgeon
I'm so shocked that I'm out of my mind
(Jeongmin) Hey, how many years has it been?
Are you still surprised?
Have you seen postpartum hemorrhage once or twice?
(Kiseon) He is
Hey, I knew it when I saw your hands earlier.
Ah, that's what a trembling aspen tree is like.
How can you do that with your hands shaking?
Do you act perfectly?
[Sound of door opening]
(Kiseon) I like it perfectly, ugh.
[Sound of door closing]
(Jaehwi) Guys
Stop it now
[cute music]
Huh?
just thank you
Ah, good job
Hey, if you did a good job, that's fine.
20 years of losing, frying, and fighting, ugh.
Ooh, ooh, I'm so sick of it
Wow, I'm bored, you guys.
Wow
[Sound of door closing]
(Kiseon) AC
Good job, good job, thank you, okay?
(Kiseon) Heh, you’re laughing.
Oh, I'm bored.
[Jeongmin’s tired exclamation]
(Jaehwi) Oh, those things
(Sabi) Professor
(Jaehwi) How did they say the surgery was over?
(Sabi) Yes?
(Jaehwi) Obstetric emergency surgery
Oh, it ended well.
(Sabi) Ah
(Jaehwi) What, where are you going?
Aren't you going?
(Sabi) Professor, I’m going to surgery.
It's a laparoscopic surgery.
I need to grab the manipulator.
(Jaehwi) Uh...
I will go there
I meant to put it in first, right?
Because Mr. Fellow is late?
(Sabi) I’m going to do that.
I also told the fellow teacher.
(Jaehwi) No, it’s okay, get off work.
There was a lot of work today
Ah...
Oh, it's okay, go
It's okay, it's okay, I can do it on my own anyway.
(Sabi) Uh...
(Jaehwi) Oh, I’m really fine.
[lively music]
(Sabi) I’m fine too.
Professor, I want to see your surgery.
(Jaehwi) Oh, oh, really?
Oh, really?
So how about I give you some RSO?
(Sabi) Good!
- thank you!
- (Jaehwi) Uh, uh, okay?
Uh, then we...
(Dowon) Yes, professor.
Maternity stable
The mother's condition was also reported to the doctor helicopter team.
I also said thank you
Yes, I will keep an eye on it.
yes
[Call end tone]
[Keyboard operation sound]
Are you done?
(Lee Young) Oh, just give me some time
Can you give me more?
(Namkyung) Ah, teacher
It's not that we didn't do it.
I couldn't do it
- Today...
- I know.
The mother asked me to say thank you?
With the teacher who spoke to me as soon as I got off the helicopter
The teacher who asked me to go to my second birthday party
That's you, right?
Today
You did really well
It must have been very scary, difficult, and crazy.
It means you did a good job or something.
I'll do the rest
(Namkyung) Yes?
Why don't you like it? Do it then
No, that's not it
Hey, go for three counts before I change my mind
one
[Nankyung’s urgent groan]
[laughter]
(Nanjing) I’ll go first.
(Lee Young) Thank you!
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
[Message incoming sound]
(Lee Young) See you there in 2 hours
(Jae-il) Aren’t you hungry?
You didn't eat anything today
(Sabi) Don’t tell me anything
I'm so hungry it's hard to walk
(Jaeil) Really?
Then do you want to eat this?
The nurse gave it to me.
Now
(Sabi) There are only two?
The kids probably didn't eat either.
just us
Shall we eat and go in?
Doesn't that seem a bit mean?
This is very famous
Sold out every day
They say if you don’t wait, you can’t buy even if you have money.
Still...
Did you see it yesterday?
- Did they fight?
- (Sabi) Yes
(Jaeil) In times like that, we need to be together.
We can't reconcile because we're embarrassed
(Sabi) Ah
Avoiding this place
It's all for them?
okay?
Then
Is that so?
Where should we go to eat?
ah!
Let's go there and eat.
Oh, there?
Yeah, if I go now, no one will be there, right?
let's go
(Ikjun) It’s been so long since I came here
Isn't this the way?
(Songhwa) No, that’s right
Turn left in front of you and go straight.
There is an escalator
If you take that down, it's the lobby.
(Ikjun) Songhwa Why don’t you know anything?
(Songhwa) It’s written
(Ikjun) Ah! Oh, I didn't see it.
Looking at other things, only looking at you
[Songhwa’s laughter]
- (Songhwa) Write it, hey, but
- (Ikjun) Yes
(Songhwa) Because I come to the outpatient clinic at night
It's a little scary
There's no one
(Ikjun) No
who is here
Who is there?
Why do you say there is something when no one is there?
Hey, don't do that.
It's not scary
(Ikjun) There are probably cockroaches here?
cockroach?
There are some cockroaches in the hospital, no way
No, not real cockroaches.
cockroaches in love
(Songhwa) Um
(Ikjun) There is no time and nowhere to meet.
I need to date
So in the hospital
You only look for places where there are no people.
(Songhwa) So where is everyone going?
Emergency stairs? On-call room?
kid!
That's where I go when I want to get caught.
Then?
[surprised gasp]
(Songhwa) Here?
[Sound of snapping fingers]
(Ikjun) That’s right
There are no outpatients at night.
There are no patients and no medical staff.
(Songhwa) Oh
(Ikjun) So secretly
I'm having a date here
Sometimes professors
I'm coming to retrieve what I left behind.
[surprised] What should I do?
- You open the door and turn on the light, right?
- (Songhwa) Oh
Then something scattered
like a cockroach
Where are you all going?
(Ikjun) Well, it’s stuck on the wall.
Hiding behind the door like this
I just went under the desk
(Songhwa) Ah
[Songhwa’s laughter]
But you
How do you know that in such detail?
Have you been hiding a lot?
(Ikjun) Oh my...
[Sound of squeezing disinfectant]
Hey, Junwan
When Junwan was a major
He said that often, I heard it too.
Ah
[shy laughter]
(Ik-jun) Write, aren’t there any here?
(Songhwa) What are you doing? Hey, don't do that.
This isn't even our hospital.
Can you hear me?
(Ikjun) What do you think you hear?
[Mysterious Music]
What is it?
[Knocking sound]
[Songhwa’s laughter]
(Ikjun) Do you think someone knocked?
(Songhwa) Ah, what can I hear?
there is no one
(Ikjun) Songhwa Did you do it?
Oh, what a surprise.
Hey, let's go
Take care today
(Songhwa) But kids these days
Wouldn't you come to a place like this?
Just holding hands in the hospital
I heard you all drank coffee?
(Ikjun) That’s the tip of the iceberg, oh my
Songhwa
People who date places like this without you knowing
There are 520 people
- Really, really.
- (Songhwa) Hey, don’t do that.
What if it's real?
[Tense sound effect]
Oh, look at that
It's all a story from the past
I heard MZs don’t do that these days.
(Ikjun) I wrote it, didn’t I?
Just last year
It took a lot for me, really.
I guess there really are no cockroaches here.
What should we have for dinner?
(Songhwa) Ah, the kids
They say I’ll have a discharge party for you quickly and for a long time.
Ramen food
(Ikjun) Oh, then I’ll buy some kimbap…
Did you tell the kids?
No, I really didn't mean to say that.
[Ikjun’s sigh]
[Songhwa’s sigh]
(Songhwa) Oh, you keep asking me where I am
When I asked when he would come, I started talking.
(Ikjun) If you know the kids
Everyone at the hospital knows this.
Oh, I'm sorry.
[Ikjun’s helpless exclamation]
Ah, if I had known this would happen, I would have gone to the hospital.
For no reason, the rumor spread all the way to Jongno.
[laughter]
[Ikjun laughs]
That's right
[Songhwa’s laughter]
[Ikjun takes a breath]
[Ikjun sighs]
[Music: Jo Jung-seok's 'Aloha']
(Songhwa) But are you really okay now?
(Ikjun) It’s not okay
I put my hands together and prayed too much
It's still hot, can you feel the heat?
[laughter]
But you almost got into big trouble.
[Ikjun’s faint sigh]
(Songhwa) Please be careful.
(Ikjun) Ah, kids
How much more will I make fun of these?
[Ikjun’s sigh]
[Songhwa’s laughter]
(Ikjun) Next to the door, why did you leave the door open?
Shouldn’t it be closed, tsk?
[Sound of door opening]
[Music stops]
went, went
(Jaeil) Oh, surprise me, Mr.
(Sabi) But
Why are we hiding?
(Residence in Japan) Huh?
Why did you tell me to hide?
It's not like I couldn't come here.
[Jaeil's embarrassed breathing]
Did I tell you to hide?
Uh, you just pushed me to the corner of the desk.
[Calm music]
(Sabi) Then stick next to me
You said ‘shh’
[Jaeil's embarrassed breathing]
Me?
[Jaeil takes a breath]
Why, why did you do that?
(Residence in Japan) No, just in case
Uh...
Oh, I'm not working
I'm afraid I'll get scolded for being here
- Did you finish your work?
- Right.
(Jaeil) Hey, even in those urgent moments, you
Do you remember everything and weigh it well?
Is it because I'm smart?
[Sound of door opening]
(Jaeil) Oh, that’s right, gown
- (Dowon) Would you like me to buy it for you?
- (Lee Young) Yes
[A wad of paper falls]
[Lee Young’s surprised exclamation]
(Dowon) A
[slaps]
[Dowon’s laughter]
[Jaeil’s surprised gasp]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
(Namkyung) Two? where?
(Dowon) What!
[Lee Young’s laughter]
- Cute
- (Namkyung) Huh? Teacher Gu Do-won?
Hey, it's really a big, big, big deal
(Jaeil) Teacher, don’t worry
Even though I'm like this, I'm a pretty loyal guy.
(Namkyung) Hello?
My name is Lee Young’s friend Pyo Nam-kyung.
Lee Young these days
(Lee Young) Don’t do it.
(Miyoung) It’s like that again, again
Holy Communion
(Miyoung) Yesterday, I cried loudly because it was my father.
How are you today, son?
(Lee Young) What are you doing now?
- You must not touch this carelessly!
- (Dawn) Oiyoung!
(Lee Young) Please just
Can’t you just work a little harder on the pain relief?
- (Dawn) What?
- (Eunmi) No, I can’t go to labor.
The baby's umbilical cord fell off!
(Namkyung) Oh, just you
All you have to do is come up quickly!
Did you see it?
(Dawn) Professor, what I asked for
You remember, right?
(Jeongmin) What does the mother mean?
Oh I-young, to the position of the housekeeper.
(Lee Young) Huh
(Jeongmin) The long legend of our mountains
Will it work for Oh Yi-young too?
(Lee Young) Where did Eom Jae-il go?
(Nanjing) Why go there at night, just the two of us?
Not a lover
Is it true that Eom Jae-il likes you?
Hey, are you guys dating?
(Sabi) Does he really like me?